(オビト)さあ… はやく！
(マダラ)させん！
神威！
Now, hurry!
Oh no, you don't!
Kamui!
The Infinite Dream
(サクラ)うっ！
(カカシ)サクラ。
Sakura!
カカシ先生…。
Kakashi Sensei.
(サクラ)サスケ君！
Sasuke?!
Why did you pop up here, Sakura?
(サスケ)なぜ サクラが
ここに出てくる？
(サクラ)時空間へ行ってたのさ。
She was in the Time-Space plane…
サクラ 向こうの状況は？
Sakura, what's going on
over there?
あっ！ カカシ先生 その左目!?
Kakashi Sensei, your left eye!
一瞬だったよ。
It all happened so quickly.
マダラに写輪眼を
奪われてしまったようだ。
But I think Madara stole my Sharingan.
診せて 先生。
Let me take a look, Sensei!
すまない。
Thanks.
それより オビトは どうなった？
In any case, what happened to Obito?
マダラが神威で
そっちへ飛んでったはずだ。
I'm sure Madara used the Kamui
to teleport himself there!
えっ 私は 急にこっちへ…。
In a flash,
I was back out here, so…
マダラ…。
Madara…
((この左目の輪廻眼を
お前が潰してくれ。
I want you to destroy my left eye,
the one that has the Rinnegan.
俺は もう動くことすらできない。
I can't even move now…
少しでも気を抜けば→
If I let down my guard,
even just a little bit…
黒ゼツに この輪廻眼ごと
体を奪われてしまう。
Black Zetsu will take over my body,
Rinnegan and all.
そうなれば 黒ゼツは
俺の右目の瞳力を使い外へ…。
Then he'll use my right eye's
Visual Prowess to get back outside…
そのまま輪廻眼が
マダラに渡ってしまう。
…and the Rinnegan will fall
into Madara's hands.
両目が揃ってしまえば
恐ろしいことになる。
If he ends up with both eyes,
terrible things will happen.
恐ろしいこと？
これ以上どうなるっていうのよ！
Terrible things?
How much worse can it get?
Hasn't he done enough?
もうイヤってほど…。
I wasn't able to implant
both Rinnegan myself.
俺も輪廻眼を両目に
移植することはできなかった。
この左目の１つでさえ→
Even with just this left eye,
強すぎるチャクラと瞳力で
己を失いかけた。
its chakra and Visual Prowess
are so strong
that I started losing myself.
本来の持ち主でない俺が→
I'm not even its original owner,
片目だけで ここまでできた。
yet I was able to accomplish
this much with just one.
本来の主に
輪廻眼の両目が戻れば→
If both Rinnegan are restored
to their true owner,
おそらく誰も
たちうちできなくなる。
I fear no one will be able
to stand against him…
そんな…。
But that's—!
瞳力とは ２つ揃って
初めて その力を発揮するもの。
With Visual Prowess,
only with both eyes together
can their full power be unleashed.
We can't waste any time.
Please destroy this left eye!
(さあ はやいほうがいい。
この左目を潰してくれ))
どうした サクラ。
What's wrong, Sakura?!
ってことは 大変じゃない。
We're in trouble!
Obito had reached his limit
and couldn't move…
オビトは
もう限界で動けなかったし…。
このままじゃ マダラに
オビトの輪廻眼をとられちゃう！
Which means Madara's going
to get Obito's Rinnegan!
The Cursed Seal Tag I placed on
your heart has disappeared.
心臓に仕込んでいた
呪印札が 消えているな。
どうやって とった？
How did you remove it?
You shouldn't have been able
to damage it yourself.
己を自分で傷つけることは
できなかったはずだ。
カカシに貫かせ 排除した。
I had Kakashi stab me
and remove it.
((カカシ : 今の俺には
これしかできない))
This is all I can do right now.
俺 自身が
十尾の人柱力になるには→
Since it was in the way
of me making myself
into the Ten Tails' Jinchuriki…
あれが 邪魔だったからな。
死ぬかもしれぬ賭けだったが→
I gambled my life on it…
俺は アンタの
思いどおりにはならないのさ。
But I wasn't going to keep
doing what you wanted!
フフフッ… いや お前は
俺の思いどおりに動いてくれた。
Actually, you did exactly
what I wanted you to do.
いや 期待以上か。
In fact, you exceeded my hopes.
なにが おかしい？
What's so funny?
操り人形にする呪印札。
A Curse Seal Tag meant to
turn you into a puppet…
仕込まれた体の中から
それを取り除こうとすれば→
One that would restrict your movements,
行動が抑制される仕組みだった。
should you try to remove it from
inside the body it's implanted in.
知っていたようだな オビト。
It seems you knew about it, Obito.
お前たちに仕込んでいた
この呪印札。
Regarding these Cursed Tags
I implanted in the two of you…
無論 自害することも
できなかったはずだ。
Naturally, you couldn't have
killed yourselves either.
Since you both were
my precious pawns.
俺にとって大切なコマだったからな。
お前たち？
"You both"…?
なんの因果か ２人とも→
As fate would have it…
It's ironic that both of
you ended up
まったく同じやり方で
排除するとは おもしろい。
getting rid of them through
the exact same method.
リン…。
そうだ。
Rin!
Yes.
あの小娘を三尾の人柱力にし→
That plot to make that girl
into the Three Tails' Jinchuriki
木ノ葉で暴れさせる計画は
俺が仕込んだことだ。
and have her rampage through
the Leaf Village was mine.
Not the Hidden Mist's!
霧隠れではない
カカシが敵に向けた技を利用して→
That girl took advantage of
Kakashi's attack against the enemy
命がけで阻止したが
あれも計画のうち。
to avert the plot,
at the cost of her life.
But that was also part
of my plan…
お前を闇へおとし
俺のコマにするためのな。
In order to pitch you
into darkness
and make you into my pawn.
You bastard, you deliberately
had me see all that!
キサマ 俺にわざと あれを…。
ミナトが別の
任務に出ていたときを狙い→
I waited for the opportunity,
カカシ一人を残して
リンを連れ出させ→
when Minato was away
on another mission.
霧隠れの忍を
操り追わせたのも すべて計画。
And manipulated the Mist Shinobi
into kidnapping Rin,
leaving Kakashi
so he would come after her.
お前の力を解放させ
そのほどを見るためでもあった。
The other purpose of that
was so I could see the extent
of your unleashed power.
白ゼツどもが お前をあおり→
Did you really think that
White Zetsu goading you on,
地下から
タイミングよく外へ出られたのも→
and you being able to get out
from underground right at that moment
すべて 偶然だと思うか？
was all a big coincidence?
((ゼツ : さっき 外行ってたんだけど。
I was just outside!
キミの言ってた
リンとバカカシってのが やばいよ！
Your friends Rin and
stupid Kakashi are in trouble!
何があった？
What happened?!
２人きりで
霧隠れの忍たちに囲まれてる。
They're alone and
completely surrounded
by Hidden Mist Shinobi!
今のリンとカカシの状況は？
How are Rin and Kakashi
doing right now?
仲間からの情報だと
かなり やばいみたいだよ。
According to the others,
it looks pretty bad.
霧隠れの実験体が
どうこうとか言ってるけど→
They're talking about some
Hidden Mist test subjects…
僕は よくわかんない。
but I don't really understand.
実験体…。
Test subjects?
Anyway, it seems Rin and
Kakashi are totally surrounded.
とにかく リンもカカシも
数十人に囲まれてるみたい。
それも みんな 凄腕の上忍や
暗部みたいのばっかだって。
And they're saying they all appear
to be jonin or Black Ops.
ミナト先生は 何してる？
What's Minato Sensei doing?
誰？
Who is that?
I'm asking you what
the Yellow Flash is doing!
黄色い閃光は何してるって
聞いてんだ！
う～ん
なんか別の任務中みたいだね。
Seems he's on a different mission.
At a time like this?!
(こんなときに…))
(マダラ)カカシの手で小娘が死んだのは
出来すぎだったがな。
That the girl dying
by Kakashi's hand
was more than I could
have hoped for.
((オビト : うお～！))
(マダラ)どっちにしろ 傀儡の忍で
殺すつもりだったんだが…。
Either way, I would have had
my Puppet Shinobi kill her.
人を操るには心の闇を利用しろと
教えたよな オビト。
I taught you to use the darkness
in people's hearts…
to manipulate them, didn't I, Obito?
くっ…。
闇がなければ作ればよい。
If there isn't any darkness,
you can create some.
自分だけが違うと思うのは
おこがましくないか？
Don't you think it's presumptuous
to consider yourself any different?
ぐっ！ なぜ…。
Why? Why me?!
なぜ 俺だったんだ!?
お前は心の底から
人に優しく 愛情深かった。
You were kind and cared about
people from the bottom of your heart.
老人介護は得意だったろう？
Remember how great you were
at taking care of the elderly?
リンへの 仲間への 火影への→
Your deep love for Rin…
for your comrades and friends…
for the Hokage and
all other shinobi…
忍への深い愛情。
いったん おちてしまえば
それは この世界への→
Once you fell into darkness,
it would conversely transform
深い憎しみへと変わるからだ。
into an equally profound
hatred for this world.
そういうヤツほどな。
くっ…。
That's the kind of guy you are.
俺の思いどおりになるには
もう少し必要なものがある。
For my plan to work completely,
I just need one more thing…
返してもらうぞ その左目を。
I'll be taking back that left eye.
(ナルト)これでよし。
This should do it!
もう動けねえぞ。
じゃあ こっち 頼んだぞ！
You can't move anymore.
I'm leaving him to you!
おう 任しとけってばよ！
Right! You can count on me!
そこに マダラが現れたらしく…。
It seems Madara appeared there.
そうか… オビトは そう言ったのか。
I see… So that's what Obito said.
マダラがいつ出てくるかも
わからない。
We don't know when Madara
might emerge. Stay alert.
気を張っておけ。
ヤツの影は どうした？
What about his shadow?
影分身と六道の棒で
ガチガチに止めてきた。
I stopped him cold with
my Shadow Clones and
Six Paths' Rods!
ナルト！
おう サクラちゃん ちょっといい？
Naruto?
Hey, Sakura…
Let me do it!
何をしようっての？ ナルト。
What are you trying to do, Naruto?
おい。
いいから いいから。
Hey!
It's okay, it's okay.
カカシ先生 目開けてみて。
Kakashi Sensei,
try opening your eye.
ウソ!? どうやって こんな…。
No way! How did you do that?
あのね 口で説明すっと
難しいんだけども→
It's really hard to explain in words…
なんか カカシ先生の一部を
ちょっと もらって→
But I took a part of Kakashi Sensei,
and then I kinda…um…uhh…
んで それにこう う～んと…。
おい
気を抜くなと言ってるんだ ナルト！
Hey, Naruto…
I told everyone to stay alert!
あ？ 俺ってば それ
初聞きなんだけど！
What?
But it's the first time
I'm hearing of it!
もう こんなときにまで
くってかかんな ナルト。
Quit talking back
for once, Naruto!
それより あとで
この目の説明を…。
Anyway, you'll have to explain
about the eye later!
マダラが カカシの目を奪い
オビトのところに行った。
Madara stole Kakashi's eye
and went to where Obito is.
次は 輪廻眼を揃えて
出てくるんだぞ。
The next time he appears,
he'll have both Rinnegan!
What? Really?
えっ そうなの!?
((カカシ : そうだな。
まずは 自己紹介してもらおう。
Let's see, we'll start
with the introductions.
俺さ 俺さ 名前は うずまきナルト。
I'll go! I'll go!
I'm Naruto Uzumaki!
好きなものは カップラーメン。
もっと好きなものは→
I love instant cup ramen.
But I really love
the ramen at Ichiraku
イルカ先生に おごってもらった
一楽のラーメン！
that Iruka Sensei treats me to
even more!
嫌いなものは
お湯を入れてからの ３分間。
I hate having to
wait three minutes
after pouring the hot water
into the cup.
将来の夢は… 火影をこす！
My future dream is…
to surpass the Hokage!
んでもって 里のヤツら全員に→
And that's why I'm going to
make everyone in the village…
俺の存在を認めさせてやるんだ！
acknowledge me!
名は うちはサスケ。
My name is Sasuke Uchiha.
嫌いなものなら
たくさん あるが→
There are lots of things I hate.
And not many things I like.
好きなものは 別にない。
それから 夢なんて言葉で
終わらす気は ないが→
Also…I have no intention of
saying I have a dream,
野望は ある。
but I do have an ambition.
ある男を 必ず 殺すことだ。
That is…
to kill a certain man one day.
私は 春野サクラ。
I'm Sakura Haruno.
好きなものは…
ていうか 好きな人は…。
What I like…I mean,
who I like is…um…
え～っと
将来の夢も言っちゃおうかな。
My future dream is…
(キャー！))
《カカシ : お前は もう
火影をこしているよ ナルト。
You've already surpassed
the Hokage, Naruto.
皆から認められ
英雄となった今も→
You're a hero and
everyone has acknowledged you.
火影を目指してる。
But becoming Hokage
is still your dream.
そして サクラ。 あのときと
サスケに対する思いは 違うだろう。
And Sakura…
I bet your feelings for Sasuke
have changed from
what they were back then.
同じ好きでも
その思いは 別のものだ。
You still love him,
but on a totally different level.
命を狙われた相手を
いまだに思う。
He tried to kill you,
yet you still care for him.
何があろうと
好いたサスケを切り捨てず→
You won't cut him off,
no matter what.
闇から救うのは
自分の役目だと思っている。
And you think it's your duty
to save him from the darkness.
お前は そういう優しい子だ。
That's how kind you are.
サスケ お前の夢は
イタチを殺すことだった。
Sasuke…
Your dream was to kill Itachi.
そして イタチ亡き今→
Now that he's gone,
what do you desire?
お前は 何を望み
どこへ進もうとしている？
What are you heading towards?
師であったにもかかわらず→
I was your teacher,
お前のことは
何も わかってやれなかった。
but it turned out that
I didn't understand you at all.
そして 今も…》
Even now…
サスケ お前の今の夢は 何だ？
Sasuke…
What is your dream now?
火影になる。
そう言った 本当の意味。
What's the true meaning
behind you saying
you'll become the Hokage?
それって…。
こうして
かつての第七班が揃ったのも→
It might be fate
that reunited the old
Team Seven like this, Sasuke.
何かの因果かもしれないな。
サスケ お前が
今 何を思っているのか→
If you don't want to say what
you're thinking right now,
俺たちに話したくないなら
それで いい。
that's fine.
(カカシ)ただ 俺たちが
第七班だったことは→
But the fact that we were
once Team 7 is undisputable…
紛れもない事実だ。
そうだろう？
Right?
前 来るよ。
In front! He's coming!
お前たち スズ取りの
最初の演習を覚えてるな？
You haven't forgotten
the lesson
from the very first mission
to steal the bells, have you?
うん！
フン！
Yes!
ったりめぇじゃん。 チームワークだ！
Of course not!
The answer is teamwork!
(マダラ)なら…。
Then dying together can also
be considered teamwork, eh?
一緒に死んでやるのも
チームワークと言うやつだろう？
マダラ 輪廻眼が揃ったか。
Madara…you have both Rinnegan.
《すでに下半身は
回復がすんでるな》
His lower body has
completely healed.
オビト！
Obito!
(ゼツ)残念だが
オビトは もういない。
Unfortunately, Obito is gone.
俺が この体をもらった。
I've taken over his body now.
コイツは自分の過ちを清算して
もらうつもりでいたようだ。
Seems he was hoping
to right his wrongs.
心の中で
お前たちに あとを頼むと→
He was praying like
a child, deep inside…
so that he could leave
the future to you all.
子供のように拝んでいたよ。
虫のいい話だろ。
How convenient that would
have been for him, right?
まるで わがままなクソガキだ。
Just like a spoiled brat.
《カカシ : 無理もない この眼力…》
I can't blame her.
Given the power of those eyes.
《綱手様 私 やっと２人に
追いつけたみたいです》
Lady Tsunade, it looks like I finally
caught up to them.
《だから もう引かない！》
I'm not retreating anymore.
私が陽動 続いて！
I'll be the diversion.
So follow me!
ちょっ！
Wait!
《サクラちゃん！》
Sakura!
((綱手 : 第四項 忍法創造再生
百豪の術を極めし医療忍者のみ→
Rule Four!
A Medic Ninja who masters
the Ninja Art of Mitotic Regeneration,
the 100 Healings,
may break the first three rules!
(上記の掟を破棄できる))
《柱間の孫娘と同じ
再生体の術か》
The same Mitotic Regeneration Jutsu
as Hashirama's granddaughter.
What?!
《サクラ : 見えない壁!? 届かない！》
An invisible wall?!
I can't reach him!
《なんだ？》
What's happening?!
うっ！
サクラちゃん。
Sakura…
気にしないで ナルト…。
Don't worry about me, Naruto.
《サスケ君は 私のこと…》
Sasuke isn't even concerned
about me…
(サクラ)大丈夫だから。
I'm all right, so…
ナルト！
ああ わかってる。
Naruto!
Yeah, I know!
There are more of them, right?
増えやがったな。
That left eye is a Rinnegan!
あの左目 輪廻眼!?
《マダラの影が ４体に増えている》
Madara's got four shadows now.
もう 余興はいい。
Enough with this sideshow.
何をする気だ？
What is he up to?
《地爆天星》
Catastrophic Planetary Devastation!
(我愛羅)いったん
ここから離れるぞ。
(リー)ナルト君たちは？
(我愛羅)ヤツなら 必ず
うまくやってくれる。
こ… これが六道の力？
前んときより でけぇし 数が違う。
上ばかり気を取られるな！
ヤツの影は こっちにいるんだぞ！
雨にしては
少し硬くて大きいがな。
来た。
影も来るぞ。
影分身の術！
任せろってばよ！
ハハハ… 俺は コイツらの死に様を
記録しておくか。
九喇嘛！
(九喇嘛)おう！
《須佐能乎！》
《尾獣玉螺旋手裏剣！》
《クソ… 次々 来る！》
《す… すごい…》
ハーッ！ ターッ！
《あの石碑の内容によれば→
輪廻の力を持つ者が
月に近づきしとき→
無限の夢を叶えるための→
月に映せし眼が開く》
世を照らせ。
無限月読。
ねえ 冬美ちゃん ドレス姿 ステキよ
よく似合ってる！
いや 幸子さんも ゴージャスです。
そう？ 派手じゃない？
ううん きれいです。
では 早速 いってみましょうか。
はい 今夜も 楽しく 華やかに…。
レッツ…。
(２人)スタート！
２時間スペシャル。